

# Gulshan Kumar

gulshan.chhablani@gmail.com

Git: https://github.com/GulshanK25

Online portfolio: https://gulshank25.netlify.app/

+46728881948 Kristianstad, Sweden

# **Professional Summary**

I am a 22-year-old student pursuing a bachelor's degree in software development. I have a strong passion for development and coding, driven by both personal interest and family inspiration. I thrive on new challenges and believe in working smart as well as hard. I am confident in my ability to contribute effectively to an organization, applying my academic knowledge and skills.

#### **Work Experience**

#### Dun & Bradstreet Europe, Stockholm, Sweden

Technology Intern June 2024 – Present

- Focused on developing and enhancing applications using Angular.
- Collaborated with the development team to implement new features and improve existing ones.
- Gained hands-on experience with industry-standard practices and tools.

# MAX Hamburger, Kristianstad, Sweden

Restaurant Assistant (Part-time) April 2023 – June 2024

• Enhanced teamwork skills and ability to handle pressure situations effectively.

# **Education**

# Kristianstad University, Kristianstad, Sweden

Bachelors in Software Development 2022 - Present

# Shaheed Zulfikar Ali Bhutto Institute of Science and Technology (SZABIST), Karachi, Pakistan

Bachelors in Computer Science 2021 - 2022

# Alpha College, Karachi, Pakistan

High School and A-Levels 2019 - 2022

#### **Skills**

# **Programming Languages:**

- Java
- Python
- C
- SQL
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript And TypeScript

#### Frameworks and Libraries:

- Node.js
- React
- Angular

# **Development Practices:**

- Agile Development (Scrum)
- Unit Testing (in Python)

### **Tools:**

- MS Visual Studio Code
- MS Visual Studio
- MySQL
- IntelliJ IDEA

- GitHub
- Jira

# **Office Software:**

- MS Word
- MS Excel

# Languages:

- English (Fluent)
- Urdu (Fluent)
- Swedish (Beginner)

# **Projects and Responsibilities**

- Managed academic projects using Jira.
- Led project presentations, demonstrating leadership and organizational skills

# **Hobbies and Interests**

- Cooking and exploring different cuisines
- Watching and playing sports such as badminton, Ping pong and Cricket
- Event management
- Learning swimming